efinancemanagement.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy | eFinanceManagement.com

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/efinancemanagement.com).  

PRIVACY POLICY

eFinanceManagement.com is owned and operated by Usha Borad. It offers useful information on Finance. By virtue of this, we take and consider online privacy very seriously and strictly. This privacy policy is designed to inform our customers/visitors to our site how we collect and use the personal information you elect to provide to us. If you are a visitor to our site and you choose to register for our services or provide us with personal information you authorize us to use such information as set forth in this privacy policy. eFinanceManagement.com collects the information necessary to serve you better.

When you visit our website, you may provide us with both personal information that you consciously choose to disclose to us on an individual basis and information that we collect when you browse this website. You may also provide us with the personal information required for us to provide the services however we only request the personal information necessary to establish and provide the necessary services requested from you.

We may however, use the personal information that you provide to us to notify you about latest updates and important changes to our web site, our services or special offers that we consider to be of importance to you on the basis of the information you have submitted. We do not share your information with any third party. The information that you provide remains with us for analyzing and concluding ways to serve you better.

Use of cookies and/or similar technology:

In case of advertisements placed on our site by third parties, these third parties often deploy persistent cookies and not session cookies, which enable them to understand and send you the right kind of advertisements, which they feel, are of interest to you. However, we do not have access and neither can we control the cookies placed by such third parties on our site. By placing the persistent cookies, the third parties can ascertain and collect information about you and where you have been using your computer to view similar advertisements.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the ****[Google ad and content network privacy policy.](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)****

Disclosure of information

We do not grant access to any personal information that you may provide to us to anyone. We do not use your information to earn any amount of profit by way of selling or leasing the same to any unaffiliated third party. We shall however, not be liable and responsible for any unauthorized access to our site by hackers who steal information, nonetheless, we take adequate precautions and measures to protect the same.

Under certain situations, we may release your personal information if required by law, or if we believe the disclosure is necessary to abide by law or to protect our web site or users of our services, or to defend our property.

Own access

You can view and edit any information provided by you to us online by registering on the website. We consider the information provided to us is vital and as a result, we advise to log out of your session each and every time you decide to end your session with our site. If you are using a public computer wherein the computer being used by you can also be used by someone else, we strictly advise to first log out and ascertain truly whether your session has truly expired or not.

Changes

We reserve the absolute right to change, amend, alter, edit, delete or add this privacy statement. In case of multiple sessions logging in by you, you are subject to two different provisions of the privacy policies, and then the most recent one shall apply. Accepting the terms and conditions as well this privacy policy automatically binds you to the most recent privacy policy applicable.

YOU ARE BOUND BY ALL THE RULES OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND THE PRIVACY POLICY IRRESPECTIVE OF WHETHER YOU HAVE READ THE SAME OR NOT. ACCESSING THIS SITE DEEMS THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD ALL THE CONTENTS OF THE TERMS OF USE, PRIVACY POLICY AND THE DISCLAIMER.
